Forget it. It's too risky.
I'm through doing that shit.
You always say that.
The same thing every time.
"l'm through, never again,
too dangerous."
I know that's what I always say.
I'm always right too.
- You forget about it in a day or two.
- The days of me forgetting are over.
The days of me remembering
have just begun.
You know, when you go on like this,
what you sound like?
- I sound like a sensible fuckin' man.
- You sound like a duck.
- Quack, quack, quack.
- Take heart, 'cause you're never
gonna have to hear it again.
Since I'm never gonna
do it again, you're never
gonna have to hear me quack.
- After tonight?
- Correct. I got all tonight to quack.
- Can I get anyone more coffee?
- Oh, yes!
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
I mean, the way it is now,
you're takin' the same risk
as when you rob a bank.
Takin' more of a risk.
Banks are easier.
Federal banks ain't supposed to stop you
in any way during a robbery.
They're insured. Why should
they give a fuck? I don't even
need a gun in a Federal bank.
Heard about this one bloke, he walks
into a bank with a portable phone.
He gives the phone to a teller.
The bloke on the other end says,
"We got this guy's little girl.
If you don't give him all your
money, we're gonna kill her."
- Did it work?
- Fuckin' right it worked.
That's what I'm talkin' about.
Knucklehead walks into a bank
with a telephone. Not a pistol,
not a shotgun, a fuckin' phone.
- Cleans the place out.
They don't lift a fuckin' finger.
- Did they hurt the little girl?
There probably never was
a little girl. The point of
the story isn't a little girl.
The point of the story is they
robbed a bank with a telephone.
- You want to rob banks?
- I'm not saying I wanna rob banks.
I'm illustrating if we did, it'd be
easier than what we've been doing.
-No more liquor stores?
-What've we been talkin' about?
Yeah, no more liquor stores.
Besides, it ain't the giggle
it used to be. There's too many
foreigners own liquor stores.
Vietnamese, Koreans,
don't even speak fuckin' English.
You tell 'em empty out
the register, they don't know
what you're talkin' about.
They make it too personal.
- We keep on, one of these gook
fuckers gonna make us kill him.
- I'm not gonna kill anybody.
I don't want to either.
But they'll probably put us
in a situation where it's us or them.
And if it's not the gooks,
it's these old fuckin' Jews who've owned
the store for 15 fucking generations.
You got Grandpa lrving sitting
behind the counter with
a fucking Magnum in his hand.
Try walkin' into one of those places
with nothing but a phone.
See how far that gets you.
Forget it.
- We're out of it.
- Well, what then, day jobs?
- Not in this life.
- What then?
Garçon, coffee!
This place.
Garçon means boy.
This place?
A coffee shop?
What's wrong with that?
Nobody ever robs restaurants.
Why not?
Bars, liquor stores,
gas stations; you get your head
blown off stickin' up one of them.
Restaurants, on the other hand,
you catch with their pants down.
They're not expectin' to get robbed.
Not as expectin' anyway.
- I bet you could cut down on the
hero factor in a place like this.
- Correct.
Same as banks,
these places are insured.
Manager.
He don't give a fuck.
They're just trying to get you out
before you start pluggin' the diners.
Waitresses. Fuckin' forget it.
No way they're takin' a bullet
for the register.
Busboys. Some wetback gettin'
paid $1.50 an hour...
really give a fuck
you're stealin' from the owner?
Customers sittin' there
with food in their mouths,
they don't know what's goin' on.
One minute, they're havin'
a Denver omelet, the next, someone
is stickin' a gun in their face.
See, I got the idea the last
liquor store we stuck up, remember?
- All the customers kept comin' in.
- Yeah.
You got the idea
of takin' their wallets.
Now, that was a good idea.
- Thank you.
- Made more from the wallets
than we did from the register.
- Yes, we did.
- A lot of people come to restaurants.
- A lot of wallets.
- Pretty smart, huh?
Pretty smart.
I'm ready. Let's do it.
Right now, right here.
- Come on.
- All right. Same as
last time, remember?
You're crowd control.
I'll handle the employees.
- I love you, Pumpkin.
- I love you, Honey Bunny.
Everybody be cool!
This is a robbery!
Any of you fucking pricks move,
and I'll execute
every motherfuckin' last one of you.
[ "Miserlou" ]
[ Radio Dial Tuning ]
[ "Jungle Boogie" ]
-  Jungle boogie
-  Get down with the boogie
-  Get it on
-  Jungle boogie
-  Get down with the boogie
-  Get it on
-  Jungle boogie
-  Get up with the boogie
-  Get up with the get down
-  Jungle boogie
-  Get down and boogie
-  Shake it around
- Okay, so tell me again
about the hash bars.
- Okay, what you want to know?
- Hash is legal there, right?
- It's legal, but it ain't 100% legal.
You just can't walk into a restaurant,
roll a joint and start puffin' away.
I mean, they want you to smoke in
your home or certain designated places.
- Those are hash bars?
- Yeah. It breaks down like this.
It's legal to buy it.
It's legal to own it.
And if you're the proprietor
of a hash bar, it's legal to sell it.
It's illegal to carry it,
but-but that doesn't matter,
'cause get a load of this.
If you get stopped by a cop
in Amsterdam, it's illegal
for them to search you.
- I mean, that's a right the cops
in Amsterdam don't have.
- Oh, man! I'm goin'.
That's all there is to it.
I'm fuckin' goin'.
I know, baby.
You'd dig it the most.
- But you know what the funniest thing
about Europe is?
- What?
It's the little differences.
I mean, they got the same shit
over there that they got here,
- but it's just there,
it's a little different.
- Example.
You can walk into a movie theater
in Amsterdam and buy a beer.
And I don't mean just like no paper cup.
I'm talkin' about a glass of beer.
And in Paris, you can buy
a beer in McDonald's.
You know what they call...
a Quarter-Pounder
with Cheese in Paris?
They don't call it
a Quarter-Pounder with Cheese?
They got the metric system.
They wouldn't know what the fuck
a Quarter-Pounder is.
- What do they call it?
- They call it a Royale with Cheese.
- Royale with Cheese.
- That's right.
What do they call a Big Mac?
Big Mac's a Big Mac,
but they call it Le Big Mac.
[ Imitating French Accent ]
Le Big Mac. [ Laughs ]
- What do they call a Whopper?
- I don't know. I didn't
go into Burger King.
- You know what they put on French fries
in Holland instead of ketchup?
- What?
- Mayonnaise. [ Chuckles ]
- Goddamn!
- I seen 'em do it, man.
They fuckin' drown 'em in that shit.
- Yuck.
We should have shotguns
for this kind of deal.
- How many up there?
- Three or four.
- That's countin' our guy?
- Not sure.
- So that means that it could be
up to five guys up there?
- It's possible.
We should have
fuckin' shotguns.
- What's her name?
- Mia.
- Mia. How did Marsellus and her meet?
- I don't know.
However people meet people.
She used to be a actress.
Oh, really?
She do anything I'd have seen?
- I think her biggest deal
was she starred in a pilot.
- Pilot? What's a pilot?
- Well, you know the shows on TV?
- I don't watch TV.
Yeah, but you are aware that there
is an invention called television,
- and on this invention
they show shows, right?
- Yeah.
The way they pick TV shows is they make
one show. That show's called a pilot.
Then they show that one show
to the people who pick shows...
and on the strength of that
one show, they decide if
they wanna make more shows.
Some get chosen and
become television programs.
Some don't, become nothin'.
She starred in one of the ones
that became nothing.
You remember
Antwan Rockamora?
Half-black, half-Samoan.
Used to call him "Tony Rocky Horror."
- Yeah, maybe. Fat, right?
- I wouldn't go so far as to
call the brother fat.
I mean, he got a weight problem.
What's a nigger gonna do? He's Samoan.
- I think I know who you mean.
What about him?
- Marsellus fucked him up good.
Word 'round the campfire is
it was on account of
Marsellus Wallace's wife.
[ Elevator Bell Rings ]
- So what he'd do? Fuck her?
- No, no, no, no, no. Nothin' that bad.
- Well, then what then?
- He gave her a foot massage.
A foot massage?
- That's it?
- Mm-hmm.
Then what'd Marsellus do?
Sent a couple cats over to his place.
They took him out on his patio.
Threw his ass over the balcony.
Nigger fell four stories.
He had a little garden down
at the bottom enclosed in glass,
like a greenhouse.
Nigger fell through that.
Since then, he kind of
developed a speech impediment.
- That's a damn shame.
- Hmm.
- But still, you play
with matches, you get burned.
- What do you mean?
You don't be givin' Marsellus Wallace's
new bride a foot massage.
You don't think he overreacted?
Antwan didn't expect Marsellus
to react the way he did,
but he had to expect a reaction.
It was a foot massage.
A foot massage is nothin'.
I give my mother a foot massage.
It's laying your hands in a familiar way
on Marsellus's new wife.
I mean, is it as bad as eatin'
her pussy out? No, but it's
the same fuckin' ballpark.
Whoa, stop right there.
Eatin' the bitch out...
and givin' the bitch a foot massage
ain't even the same fucking thing.
- It's not. It's the same ballpark.
- Ain't no fuckin' ballpark neither.
Now, look, maybe your method
of massage differs from mine.
But touchin' his wife's feet
and sticking your tongue
in the holiest of holies...
ain't the same fuckin' ballpark;
it ain't the same league;
it ain't the same fuckin' sport.
- Foot massages don't mean shit!
- Have you ever given a foot massage?
[ Scoffs ]
Don't be tellin' me about foot massages.
- I'm the foot fuckin' master.
- You given a lot of them?
Shit, yeah!
Got my technique down and everything.
I don't be ticklin' or nothin'.
Would you give a guy
a foot massage?
- Fuck you.
- [ Chuckles ]
- You give 'em a lot?
- Fuck you.
- You know, I'm kind of tired.
I could use a foot massage.
- Yo, yo, yo, man.
You best back off.
I'm gettin' a little pissed here.
- This is the door.
- Yeah, it is.
What time you got?
7:22 in the a.m.
No, it ain't quite time yet.
Come on. Let's hang back.
Look, just 'cause I wouldn't give no man
a foot massage don't make it right...
for Marsellus to throw
Antwan off a building into
a glass motherfuckin' house,
fuckin' up the way the nigger talks;
that shit ain't right.
Motherfucker do that shit to me,
he better paralyze my ass,
'cause I kill the motherfucker.
I ain't sayin' it's right,
but you sayin' a massage don't mean
nothin'. I'm sayin' it does.
Now, look, I've given a million
ladies a million foot massages,
and they all meant somethin'.
We act like they don't,
but they do. That's what's
so fuckin' cool about them.
There's a sensuous thing goin' on...
where you don't talk about it,
but you know it and she knows it.
Fuckin' Marsellus knew it. And Antwan
should've fuckin' better known better.
That's his fuckin' wife, man.
This ain't a man with a sense
of humor about this shit.
You know what I'm sayin'?
It's an interestin' point.
Come on.
Let's get into character.
- What's her name again?
- Mia.
- Why you so interested
in big man's wife?
He's goin' out of town, Florida.
And he asked me if I'd take care
of her while he's gone.
- Take care of her?
- No, man. Just take her out.
Show her a good time.
Make sure she don't get lonely.
You're gonna be takin'
Mia Wallace out on a date?
It is not a date.
It's just like if you were
gonna take your buddy's wife
to a movie or somethin'.
- It's just good company, that's all.
- [ Sighs ]
- It's not a date.
It's definitely not a date.
- [ Sighs ]
Hey, kids.
How you boys doin'?
Hey, keep chillin'.
You know who we are?
We're associates of your
business partner, Marsellus Wallace.
You do remember
your business partner, don't you?
Now, let me take
a wild guess here.
- You're Brett, right?
- Yeah.
I thought so. You remember
your business partner Marsellus Wallace,
don't ya, Brett?
Yeah, I remember.
Good. Looks like me and Vincent
caught you boys at breakfast.
Sorry about that.
Whatcha havin'?
Hamburgers.
Hamburgers! The cornerstone
of any nutritious breakfast.
What kind of hamburgers?
- Uh, ch-cheeseburgers.
- No, no, no.
Where'd you get 'em?
McDonald's, Wendy's, Jack-in-the-Box?
- Where?
- Uh, Big Kahuna Burger.
Big Kahuna Burger!
That's that Hawaiian burger joint.
I hear they got some tasty burgers.
I ain't never had one myself.
How are they?
They're-- They're good.
You mind if I try
one of yours?
- This is yours here, right?
- Yeah.
Mmmm.
This is a tasty burger!
Vincent!
You ever had
a Big Kahuna burger?
Want a bite?
They're real tasty.
- I ain't hungry.
- Well, if you like burgers,
give 'em a try sometime.
Me, I can't usually get 'em
'cause my girlfriend's a vegetarian,
which pretty much makes me
a vegetarian.
But I do love the taste
of a good burger. Mmmm.
You know what they call
a Quarter-Pounder with Cheese
in France?
- No.
- Tell 'em, Vincent.
- A Royale with Cheese.
You know why they call it that?
Uh, because of
the metric system?
Check out the big brain
on Brett!
You're a smart motherfucker.
That's right. The metric system.
- What's in this?
- Sprite.
Sprite. Good.
You mind if I have some of your
tasty beverage to wash this down with?
Go right ahead.
[ Slurping, Sighs ]
That hit the spot.
You. Flock of Seagulls.
You know why we're here?
- Why don't you tell my man
Vince here where you got the shit hid.
- It's over--
I don't remember askin' you
a goddamned thing!
You were sayin'?
It's in the cupboard.
N-No, the one
by your kn-knees.
[ Pans Rattling ]
[ Rattling Continues ]
[ Hit Man ]
We happy?
Vincent?
- We happy?
- Yeah, we happy.
[ Sighs ]
[ Brett ] Look, I'm sorry, uh, l--
I didn't get your name.
I got yours. Vincent. Right?
B-But I never got yours.
- My name's Pitt, and your ass
ain't talkin' your way outta this shit.
- No, no, no.
I just want you
to know how--
I just want you to know how sorry we are
th-that things got so fucked up...
with us and Mr. Wallace.
W-We got into this thing with
the best intentions. Really. I never--
Oh, I'm sorry,
did I break your concentration?
- [ Gasping ]
- I didn't mean to do that. Please.
Continue. You were saying something
about "best intentions."
What's the matter?
Oh, you were finished!
Oh, well, allow me to retort.
What does Marsellus Wallace
look like?
What?
- What country you from?
- What?
- "What" ain't no country I ever
heard of. They speak English in What?
- W-What?
- English, motherfucker!
Do you speak it?
- Yes!
- Then you know what I'm sayin'!
- Yes.
Describe what Marsellus Wallace
looks like!
- What? l--
- Say "what" again!
Say "what" again! I dare ya!
I double dare you, motherfucker!
- Say "what" one more goddamn time!
- H-H-He's black.
- Go on!
- He's bald!
- Does he look like a bitch?
- What?
- [ Gunshot ]
- [ Screaming ]
Does he look... Iike a bitch?
- No!
- Then why you tryin'
to fuck him like a bitch?
- I didn't.
- Yes, you did. Yes, you did, Brett!
- You tried to fuck him.
- [ Gasping ] No, no.
But Marsellus Wallace don't like to be
fucked by anybody except Mrs. Wallace.
- You read the Bible, Brett?
- Yes!
Well, there's this passage
I got memorized. Sort of
fits this occasion.
Ezekiel 25:17.
"The path of the righteous man...
is beset on all sides
by the inequities of the selfish...
and the tyranny of evil men.
Blessed is he who,
in the name of charity and goodwill,
shepherds the weak
through the valley of darkness,
for he is truly
his brother's keeper...
and the finder
of lost children.
And I will strike down upon thee
with great vengeance...
and furious anger...
those who attempt to poison
and destroy My brothers!
And you will know
My name is the Lord...
when I lay My vengeance
upon thee!"
[ Screams ]
[ "Let's Stay Together" ]
[ Man ]
I think you gonna find...
when all this shit
is over and done--
I think you're gonna find yourself
one smilin' motherfucker.
The thing is, Butch,
right now...
you got ability.
But painful as it may be,
ability... don't last.
And your days are just about over.
Now, that's a hard
motherfuckin' fact of life.
But that's a fact of life your ass
is gonna have to get realistic about.
You see, this business is filled to
the brim with unrealistic motherfuckers.
Motherfuckers who thought
their ass would age like wine.
If you mean it turns
to vinegar... it does.
If you mean it gets better
with age... it don't.
Besides, Butch,
how many fights you think
you got in you anyway?
Hmm?
Two?
Boxers don't have
an old-timers' day.
You came close,
but you never made it.
And if you were gonna make it,
you would have made it before now.
[ Music Continues ]
You my nigger?
Certainly appears so.
[ Chuckles ]
The night of the fight,
you may feel a slight sting.
That's pride fuckin' with you.
Fuck pride!
Pride only hurts.
It never helps.
You fight through that shit.
'Cause a year from now,
when you kickin' it in the Caribbean,
you gonna say to yourself,
"Marsellus Wallace was right."
[ Chuckles ]
I got no problem
with that, Mr. Wallace.
In the fifth,
your ass goes down.
Say it.
In the fifth,
my ass goes down.
Yo, Vincent Vega.
Our man in Amsterdam.
Jules Winfield, our man in lnglewood.
Get your asses on in here.
- Goddamn, nigger,
what's up with them clothes?
- You don't even want to know.
Where's the big man?
The big man's right over there
takin' care of some business.
Why don't you hang back a second or two.
You see the white boy leave, go on over.
[ Vincent ]
How ya been?
- I been doin' pretty good.
How 'bout yourself?
- All right.
So I hear you're
takin' Mia out tomorrow.
At Marsellus's request.
- Have you met Mia?
- Not yet.
- [ Chuckles ]
- What's so fuckin' funny?
- Not a goddamn thing.
- I got to piss.
Look, I'm not a fuckin' idiot,
all right? It's the big man's wife.
I'm gonna sit across from her,
chew my food with my mouth closed,
Iaugh at her fuckin' jokes,
and that's it.
Hey, my name's Paul,
and this shit's between y'all.
Then what'd you fuckin'
ask me about it for?
[ Whispers ]
Asshole.
- Gimme a pack of Red Apples.
- Filters?
No.
- You lookin' at somethin', friend?
- You ain't my friend, palooka.
-What was that?
-I think you heard me just fine, punchy.
Vincent Vega's in the house?
My nigger,
get your ass over here.
- What's up?
- Man, I'm really sorry.
You shouldn't worry about it.
Pack of Red Apples. $1.40.
And some matches.
Thanks.
[ Woman ] It's as if it turns every part
of your body into the tip of a penis.
- Whoa.
- I'll lend it to you.
It's a great book on piercing.
That gun to pierce your ears,
they don't use that to pierce
your nipples, do they?
Forget that gun. That guns goes against
the entire idea behind piercing.
All my piercing, 18 places on my body,
every one of 'em done with a needle.
Five in each ear, one through
the nipple of my left breast,
two in my right nostril,
one in my left eyebrow,
one in my belly,
one in my lip, one in my clit,
- and I wear a stud in my tongue.
- [ Vincent ] Excuse me.
I was just curious,
but, um... why would you wear
a stud in your tongue?
Sex thing.
Helps fellatio.
Vincenzo.
Step in my office.
This is Panda from Mexico.
Very good stuff.
Now, that's Bava.
Different, but equally good.
And that is Choco
from the Harz Mountains of Germany.
Now, the first two are the same.
300 a gram. Those are friend prices.
But this one
is a little more expensive.
This is 500 a gram.
But, when you shoot it, you will know
where that extra money went.
There's nothing wrong with these two.
This is real, real, real good shit.
But this one
is a fuckin' madman.
Remember, I just got back
from Amsterdam.
Am I a nigger?
Are we in lnglewood? No.
You're in my home. Now, white people
who know the difference...
between good shit and bad shit,
this is the house they come to.
Now, my shit, I'll take the Pepsi
Challenge with that Amsterdam shit...
- any old day of the fuckin' week.
- That's a bold statement.
This ain't Amsterdam, Vince.
This is a seller's market.
Coke is fuckin' dead
as... dead.
Heroin, it's comin' back
in a big fuckin' way.
- All right.
Gimme three grams of madman.
- Okay.
Now, if it's as good as you say it is,
I'll come back and buy another thousand.
I just hope that I still
have some left for ya,
but I'm givin' you some
out of my own private stash.
That is what a nice guy I am.
- I'm outta balloons.
Is a baggie all right?
- Yeah, that's cool.
All right.
I'll just get one for ya.
Honey, will you get me some baggies
and, uh, twistix from the kitchen?
[ Woman ]
Okay.
Hey, uh, what do you think about Trudi?
She ain't got a boyfriend.
- You wanna hang out and get high?
- Which one's Trudi?
-The one with all the shit in her face?
-No, that's Jody.
That's my wife.
- [ Chuckles ] I'm sorry, man.
- Thank you.
- No, I can't. I gotta be someplace.
- All right, no problemo.
- I'll take a rain check.
- [ Knocking ]
- Oh.
- Thank you, Jody.
Still got your Malibu?
Oh, man, you know what some fucker
did the other day?
- What?
- Fuckin' keyed it.
- Oh, man, that's fucked up.
- Tell me about it.
I had it in storage
for three years.
It was out five days, and some
dickless piece of shit fucked with it.
They should be fuckin' killed,
man. No trial, no jury,
straight to execution.
I wish I could've caught him
doin' it. I'd have given
anything to catch that asshole.
- It'd been worth him doin' it
just so I could've caught him.
- What a fucker!
What's more chicken-shit
than fuckin' with a man's automobile?
- Don't fuck with another man's vehicle.
- You don't do it.